so let's go over how you can change the
因此，让我们回顾一下如何更改
perspective of an object using inkscape
使用Inkscape的对象的透视
for this demonstration I'll be using a
在本演示中，我将使用
text object so I'm going to grab my text
对象，所以我要获取我的文本
tool and I'm going to click on the
工具，我将点击
canvas and I'm just going to use the
Canvas和我将使用
word perspective for this demonstration
本演示的Word视角
and then I'm going to grab my selection
然后我要拿出我的选择
tool and I'm going to make this a little
工具，我要把这个做得有点
bit bigger so you can see it better
大一点，这样你就能看得更清楚了
now what we want to do is open up our
现在我们要做的是开放我们的
pathfx menu so I'll come up here to
所以我会到这里来
where it says path and I will select
上面写着路径，我会选择
pathfx
路径FX
now in order for this function to work
现在，为了使此功能发挥作用
the object that we're applying it to has
我们要将其应用于的对象具有
to be a path right now this is just a
现在成为一条道路，这只是一条
text object so let's convert this to a
对象，因此让我们将其转换为
path by going to path object to path and
路径：转到路径对象到路径，然后
once you've done that you should be able
一旦你做到这一点，你应该能够
to click on this little plus icon down
向下点击这个加号小图标
here in the menu to add a new path
在菜单中添加新路径
effect and the path effect that we're
影响和路径效应，我们是
looking for is called perspective
寻找是所谓的透视
envelope which is located right there if
位于那里的信封，如果
you're having trouble accessing it you
你在访问它时遇到了麻烦
could just type it into the search bar
只需在搜索栏中输入即可
up here per s and there it is
按照S的说法，这就是它
perspective envelope
透视包络
and now all you have to do is grab your
现在你要做的就是拿起你的
edit paths by nodes tool and if you look
按节点编辑路径工具，如果您查看
in the corners over here you will see
在这里的角落里，你会看到
these four white nodes and you can take
这四个白色节点，你可以
these nodes and use it to change the
这些节点，并使用它来更改
perspective of your object just like
对象的透视图，就像
that
那
now if you want to lock the perspective
现在，如果您想锁定透视图
onto a certain axis you can use these
在某个轴上，您可以使用这些
settings over here in the pathfx menu so
在pathfx菜单中进行设置，以便
if I select mirror movements in on the
如果我在上选择了镜像移动
horizontal axis it'll make it so that
水平轴它会让它变得
the perspective only changes relative to
透视图仅相对于以下内容更改
the horizontal axis like that as you can
像这样的水平轴
see there and likewise if you use
请看这里，如果您使用
vertical it'll lock the perspective
垂直，它会锁定透视
change onto the vertical axis like that
像这样转到垂直轴上
and once you are finished you can
一旦你完成了，你就可以
finalize the changes by going to path
通过转到PATH完成更改
object to path and you are done that is
对象到路径，你就完成了，也就是说
how you can change the perspective of an
如何改变一个
object using inkscape if you found this
如果您发现这个，则使用inkscape对象
lesson useful then consider checking out
课程有用，然后考虑查看
my inkscape master class it's a
我的水墨风景大师班是一堂
collection of over 60 videos where I go
收集了我去过的60多个视频
over all of the tools and features in
中的所有工具和功能
inkscape and I explain what they are and
inkscape和我解释了它们是什么，
demonstrate how they work kind of like
演示它们的工作原理有点像
how I did in this video we even have a
我在这个视频中的表现我们甚至有一个
private Community where you can ask
私人社区，您可以询问
questions and get help from me anytime
随时向我提问并寻求帮助
you want and best of all there's no
你想要的，最重要的是没有
monthly membership fees you just pay 17
每月只需支付17美元会员费
one time and you're in for Life I'll
一次，你就会终身监禁我会
have some information about that down
有一些相关信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想检查一下，请在下面作为
always thanks for watching
始终感谢观看